[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "If I cut off your cord to everything else and left you with one thing, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "I guess play piano, you know, because that's the thing I started doing when I was a little kid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "``", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "You were playing Mozart at the age of 5, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "No, I was playing \"When the Saints Go Marching In\" at the age of 5.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mozart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "When was the moment you thought, this could be more than just a hobby, this could be -- this could be my lifetime thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", ":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, my dad was the district attorney of New Orleans for about 30 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "You can't buy it, can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "No, you really can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "If somebody older than you walked in the room, you should stand up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "She had cancer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Did you realize that she was dying or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I knew she was not feeling well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "He still lives in New Orleans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "He still lives there and he's in great health and he's handsome and strong and got an incredible moral and ethical backbone.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What would she have made of what's happened to you, your mom did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Oh my gosh, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "When did you hear about it and how quickly did you realize how bad it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I heard about it on -- I knew the storm was coming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "And when you got there and saw the scale of devastation -- I mean, as someone who had been born there, raised there, what was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "EX", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "It's hard to articulate, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Why was it not just obvious there was this awful disaster unfurling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Well, I'm not privy to all of the details that unfolded and led people to make certain decisions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "I -- you know, at this point, what good is it going to do to blame local or state or federal government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Some people, you know, said it was kind of surreptitious racism, that it was the fact that there were so many poor black people meant that the authorities didn't respond in the way, if they had all been middle class white people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "And what is New Orleans like these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Awesome.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Was he scathing of the authorities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "You know, we never really talked about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "-- underneath this gentle cheery exterior.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "How many people do you think have made love to your music over the years, Harry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I don't know if I want to think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Because when she makes me put out the trash, seduction isn't part of that order, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "When I thought you couldn't get any more sickening in terms of the perfect life and career, I remembered that you actually married a Victoria's Secret model.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "How did you wangle that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Oh, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "-- throw themselves at you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "When you say been with, what do you mean, Harry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Doing movies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "You talking about another way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "ORGAN: I wasn't quite sure if I was losing a bit of --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Did you ever meet Frank Sinatra?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I did, on a few occasions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "What does he think of you as the young upstart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "ONNICK: Oh, I don't think he thought of me like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I mean, this guy had 40, 50 years of people saying that they were upstarts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Did he give you any advice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "The closest thing to advice that he gave me was when I asked him how he hit this high A flat -- we did have a similar range.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "I mean, it's not great advice, because you need to be Frank Sinatra for it to work, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Is that -- was that a technical thing that he had over other people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I don't -- I wouldn't say that was what made him great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "And that one piece of advice he gave you, have you been able to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I still can't hit that note.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beverly Hilton", "LA"]}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Were you there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "-- at the Beverly Hilton in LA.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Do you -- do you remember that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "I was --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Do you remember how bad I was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "You were terrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "He didn't even reply to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "He didn't even look at me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "But, I mean generally, do -- do you get fired up politics, by what's going on to your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "I like to watch sort of from afar and learn what I can, just as a citizen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 661, "question": "-- do you watch the debates?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "I do enjoy --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", ":", "IN", "VB", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Are you -- do you -- do you veer to either party or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "I think, you know, right now it's -- it's interesting to -- to see what everyone has to say and what --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Out of the Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Did you vote Obama last time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Can he sing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Yes, he really can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Are you going to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I'd like to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "When is it launching?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Previews start November the 12th.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "And I'm assuming there will be some hot tickets for me here, Harry, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Standing room only.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "-- to America?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "I think you should sing to me, because it will look more awkward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]